http://www.larkspurchicago.com/privacy-policy

Send Flowers
Privacy Policies AnalyticsThis website collects personal data to power our site analytics, including:Information about your browser, network, and deviceWeb pages you visited prior to coming to this websiteYour IP addressThis information may also include details about your use of this website, including:ClicksInternal linksPages visitedScrollingSearchesTimestampsWe share this information with Squarespace, our website analytics provider, to learn about site traffic and activity.CookiesThis website uses cookies and similar technologies, which are small files or pieces of text that download to a device when a visitor accesses a website or app. For information about viewing the cookies dropped on your device, visit About the cookies Squarespace uses.These functional and required cookies are always used, which allow Squarespace, our hosting platform, to securely serve this website to you.These analytics and performance cookies are used on this site, as described below, only when you acknowledge our cookie banner. We use analytics cookies to view site traffic, activity, and other data.Customer accountsIf you create a customer account on this website, we collect personal information to improve our checkout experience and customer service.This information may include your:Billing and shipping address(es)Details about your orders (for example, your shirt size)Email addressNamePhone numberWe share this information with Squarespace, our website hosting provider, so they can provide website services to us.EmailsAbandoned cart emailsYou’ll receive an automated email within 24 hours after you abandon your shopping cart, if all of the following occur:You enter your email address at checkout, or are logged into your Customer Account.You add a product which is in stock to your shopping cart.You close your browser or leave this website without completing your purchase.You can unsubscribe from these messages at the bottom of the email.The email will link back to this website, where you can pick up where you left off and complete your purchase.Marketing emailsWe may send you marketing emails, which you can unsubscribe from by clicking the link at the bottom of the email. We share your contact information with Squarespace, our email marketing provider, so they can send these emails on our behalf.Order and account emailsWe may email you with messages about your order or account activity. For example, we may email you to tell you that:You’ve created a Customer AccountYour Customer Account password has been reset or updatedYou’ve made a purchaseYour order has shippedIt’s not possible to unsubscribe from these messages.We share your contact information with Squarespace, our website hosting provider, so they can send these emails to you on our behalf.FontsThis website uses font files from Google Fonts and Adobe Fonts. To properly display this site to you, servers where the font files are stored may receive personal information about you, including:Information about your browser, network, or deviceYour IP addressVisitor dataFor customersWhen you buy something on this website, we collect personal information from you to fulfill the order. We may collect information like your:Billing and shipping addressDetails relating to your purchase (for example, your shirt size)Email addressNamePhone numberWe share this information with Squarespace, our online store hosting provider, so that they can provide website services to us.As you go through checkout, this site may auto-complete your shipping and billing address by sharing what you type with the Google Places API and returning suggestions to you to improve your checkout experience.For website visitorsThis website is hosted by Squarespace. Squarespace collects personal data when you visit this website, including:Information about your browser, network and deviceWeb pages you visited prior to coming to this websiteYour IP addressSquarespace needs the data to run this website, and to protect and improve its platform and services. Squarespace analyzes the data in a de-personalized form.
